During one of the Sunday services at The SCOAN,
the evangelists are sent by Prophet T.B. Joshua to move in the midst of the congregation
and minister the Morning Water in the name of Jesus Christ.
Remember, the Bible says in the book of Acts 19, that anything that had come into contact
with Apostle Paul was taken to the afflicted and the oppressed
and they received healing and deliverance.
As it was, so it is.
Jesus Christ is the same yesterday, today and forever.
And He can use any medium to express Himself and His mission to others.
As this instrument of God's power descends upon the people,
the reaction is as instant as it is awesome.
Darkness flees.
Unclean spirits are exposed and people are restored to the original position in which God created them.
Total liberty of spirit, soul and body.
Among the congregants is this lady who immediately looses control of her faculties
as the Morning Water is ministered.
Let's watch the spiritual battle that follows.
Now speak! Who are you in this body?
Speak! Who are you in this body, you demon?
Who are you in this body?
Leave me alone!
Speak out! Who are you in this body?
In the name of Jesus Christ, in the blood of Jesus Christ, you have no choice.
And you can't resist this - this is the power of God.
Speak, in the name of Jesus Christ! Who are you in this body?
I am a queen.
As a queen, what have you done to her?
I am the queen of this body.
I destroyed everything around and inside her.
Speak in the name of Jesus Christ! What have you destroyed?
Name what you have destroyed, you demon.
I destroyed her health.
You have destroyed her health. Mention the sickness you have given her.
She has no faith in your God.
Speak, in the name of Jesus' Christ.
She is unhappy; I destroyed everything in her life.
I destroyed her marriage and will make her divorce.
She will be unhappy until the end of her life.
Now, listen to this!
You demon, speak! Mention what you have done to her marriage.
Speak, in the name of Jesus Christ!
What have you done to her marriage?
I irritate him all the time.
Who is this man standing beside you? Who is he? Speak!
This is her husband.
Ok, this is her husband.
Mention what you have done to her marriage.
I want them to divorce.
You want them to divorce. Now explain - what are the things you have made her to do?
What have you caused this woman to do in her marriage? Explain.
I have many powers; I can make people worship me.
What else have you done to her family?
What else have you done to her?
Apart from her marital life, what else have you done to her?
I told you she is unhappy. Her mother and sister are unhappy; she will be unhappy all her life.
He irritates me because he prays all the time.
Who made her to be depressed?
And what do you want her to do because of her unhappiness?
She only thinks about her illnesses.
What do you want her to do due to her unhappiness and depression?
What do you want her to do, you demon? Speak!
I want to separate them so that she can do whatever I want.
It is painful for me.
You are welcome, sir. Who is she to you?
She is my wife.
Can you tell us what you can say about your wife?
She has mentioned that the demon wants both of you to be separated.
What can you say about that?
Yes, the demon always makes her irritate me.
It tries to make us always unhappy and have a confrontation.
Tell us about her character, how she behaves at home, and how she causes trouble.
She can't pray or read anything spiritual. Her spiritual life is zero.
She can't do anything in terms of praying and believing.
She mentioned that this demon caused her to be unhappy
and caused everybody in the house to be sad. What can you say about that?
The demon tries to make her aggressive and depressed.
Who caused her depression? Who made her to be depressed?
Speak, in the name of Jesus' Christ! Who made her to be depressed?
I caused it. I can cause it to anyone here.
What else have you done to her?
She will be alone and she will never have children.
How did you enter her?
When she was born, I was there. I'm from generations.
By the special grace of God, the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, has sent this Morning Water
to deliver you and today is the end.
Fire all over your body, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Your time has expired in this body and today is the last day.
You have to leave.
Come here!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Out of this body, in the name of Jesus!
Out of this body!
Out!
Fire all over your body, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Out of this body!
Out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
I hate you!
You have no choice.
The power of God is more than you. Jesus owns all authority.
Out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Out!
Out of her!
Out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Come here!
I have lived here for centuries. Do you want me to come out?
No matter how long you have been in this body, you demon, today is your end.
You have to leave this body and go to the pit of hell.
Now, Jesus wants you to leave. Out of this body!
Out!
Out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
In Jesus' mighty name we pray.
Thank You, Jesus, for her deliverance.
In Jesus' name. You are free.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Stand up, Madam, you are free in the name of Jesus Christ,
through the medium of the Morning Water sent by Prophet T.B. Joshua.
You are free in Jesus' name.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus, we are free. Thank You, Jesus.
So who is this man standing beside you?
He is my husband.
Now Jesus Christ has set you free through the medium of the Morning Water sent by Prophet T.B. Joshua,
and today Jesus Christ has declared you free. Continue to walk in the light of your testimony.
Sir, whatever she has said today, please do not remind her of her past.
Her past is over and you continue to live for Christ Jesus from now henceforth, in Jesus' name.
Thank You, Jesus.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Mrs Elmira Pak & Husband
Kazakhstan
Good morning, Church. Her name is Elmira, we came from Kazakhstan and I am her husband.
Tell us your testimony.
Mrs Elmira Pak & Husband
Deliverance Testimony
When we got married, we noticed that she had the spirit of anger
and we understood that we needed to do something about it.
So we went to different churches to get this deliverance but there was no help.
We have heard it from the woman that the problem that brought her to The SCOAN
was that she was possessed with a demon that caused her a terrible spirit of anger.
She has been to several places and churches for deliverance all to no avail.
They both deemed it necessary to visit The SCOAN for her deliverance.
Tell us how this spirit of anger affected your life, your marriage and everything that has to do with you,
before you came for deliverance.
Mrs Elmira Pak & Husband
Deliverance Testimony
She said that we had a normal family, no problems with money, shelter, job,
but she felt very disturbed, caring a lot about different things.
She would become angry because of small things that were happening not the way she wanted them to.
She wanted everything to be her way.
We have heard it from the husband.
He explained that the spirit of anger affected the marriage in the sense that
she got angry at every little thing and she always wanted her own will to supersede his,
until they finally came to The SCOAN for deliverance.
Tell us how you come to know about The SCOAN.
Mrs Elmira Pak & Husband
Deliverance Testimony
She said that after we recognised the problem, we started to search for help
and we saw a video on YouTube where there was deliverance in The SCOAN
and I as her husband started to pray and to prepare, since the beginning of the year to come here.
Because of the terrible problem of this spirit of anger, they started looking for a solution.
That was how they went on the internet and as God would have it,
they came across Emmanuel TV.
That's how both of them came together and decided to visit The SCOAN for her deliverance.
Tell us what happened last Sunday when the evangelist ministered the Morning Water on you.
Mrs Elmira Pak & Husband
Deliverance Testimony
When the Morning Water ministration started, she looked around and saw many people
who were to minister the Morning Water and she began to worry.
After the evangelist started ministering the Morning Water on her,
she doesn't remember from that moment what was happening. She couldn't understand it.
She could understand everything in her mind but she could not control her speech and actions.
You have heard the husband interpret what she rightly said.
While the evangelist was ministering the Morning Water,
before the evangelist got to where she was, she started feeling worried and uncomfortable.
The moment the evangelist ministered the Morning Water on her, she lost consciousness of herself.
At the end of the day, she found herself being delivered.
Tell us, ever since you have been delivered,
what are the changes you have seen in your life, to really confirm
that the spirit of anger has left you completely.
Mrs Elmira Pak & Husband
Deliverance Testimony
She said that since the deliverance, she feels calm and peaceful. She has peace inside her.
She trusts God, she trusts me as her husband and she has no urge to be in control.
Before, she had a problem with belief because the spirit always tried to make her focus on her problems.
She could not read and grow in her faith.
But now, she feels stronger spiritually.
To God be the glory.
You have heard the husband.
She said that ever since the deliverance took place,
she has seen tremendous changes in her life and also in her marriage.
She is no longer authoritative in her marriage, she no longer wants her will to supersede that of her husband,
she is very calm now and does not see herself getting angry at every little thing.
She said the area that baffled her most was that before her deliverance,
each time she wanted to read the Word of God, she would find herself thinking about her past.
For that reason, she would lose concentration.
But after the deliverance, she developed love for the Word of God,
she can read and fully concentrate.
She is giving thanks to God Almighty for restoring her concentration to the will of God.
Put your hands together beautifully for the miracle working God!
Finally, what word of advice do you have for those who are listening to you around the world?
Mrs Elmira Pak & Husband
Deliverance Testimony
She said that if you feel disappointed or have some doubts about God's power,
just belief in God, stay faithful to Him.
Wherever you are does not matter. Just belief in God and you will see His glory.
To God be the glory. You have heard it all.
That if you feel disappointed and belief that the power of God does not exist,
all you need to do is to belief and trust in Him
because God is powerful and faithful to those who are faithful to Him as well.
Let's put our hands together beautifully for that!
Sir, could you introduce yourself to us? Who are you to her?
My name is Igor Pak. I am her husband.
What do you have to say about her testimony?
Actually it is true because sometimes I would notice that her faith was weak.
She could not read the Word, she could not pray,
she was always disturbed about some other things beside God.
Now I see that her character has changed.
You mean after her deliverance?
After the deliverance, I can see that she has changed, she has peace,
and she is not disturbed all the time.
You have heard the husband testifying to the goodness of the Lord in the life of his wife after her deliverance.
Prior to her deliverance, he could see that the wife had lost total concentration concerning the things of God,
she didn't read her Bible and she didn't talk about God
because of that terrible spirit of anger that almost destroyed her life.
But he is giving glory to God Almighty that after the wife has been delivered,
he has witnessed numerous changes in her life.
Right now, she can read the Word of God with full concentration.
She has peace in her heart and the family is united once again.
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ for that!
As the husband, what word of advice do you have?
My advice to husbands is that you should not panic.
Trust in God. He is faithful.
Prayers are always heard by God and He is prepare the answer for you. Glory be to God.
Amen! In other words, prayers for many years are not lost,
they are issuing themselves out in glory, slowly but surely.
Don't lose your faith in God, put your faith in God and trust in Him alone.
For He alone can surprise you in every situation.
To God be the glory. We thank God Almighty for your lives
and we also rejoice with you for this wonderful transformation.
We want to advise you by saying that you should make the Word of God the standard for your lives
so that your deliverance will remain permanent, in Jesus' name.
Let's clap for Jesus Christ!